Mss.B.H357.p
American Philosophical Society
- I. Correspondence
  - Corwin, Margaret T
  - Cory, Mrs. John Virgil
  - Cosmopolitan
  - Cosmopolitan Club
  - Cosmopolitan Transfer Co.
  - Cosmos Club
  - Costello, J J
  - Costello, Pat
  - Cotter, Edward J
  - Council of Social Agencies
  - Council on Pharmacy and Chemistry
  - Covington, P W
  - Cowans, Mrs. W B
  - Cowgill, George R
  - Cox, J H
  - Crabites, Pierre
  - Crabtree Will and Vivisection
  - Craft, Howard E
  - Craig, Austin
  - Craig, Helen
  - Cramer, P E
  - Crampton, C Ward
  - Crane, J B
  - Cranfill, J B
  - Craven, Mrs. George
  - Crawford, Alfred R
  - Crawshaw, F A
  - Crews, F C
  - Crile, George
  - Crimmins, Thomas
  - Crispin, Egerton
  - Crissman, Edwarda H
  - Croke, John J
  - Crooks, F Raymond
  - Cross, W J
  - Crossette, Virginia Maverick
  - Crotty, Bros. Inc.
  - Crouch, H A
  - Crouzet, Eva C
  - Crow, Fay
  - Crowder
  - Crowell Mfg. Co.
  - Crowell, B C
  - Crown-Zellerbach Corp.
  - Crug, Mrs. Herbert
  - Crum, E R
  - Crum, Grace R
  - Crum, Mary M
  - Crusaders for Better Milk
  - Culbertson, Ely
  - Culbertson, La Monte
  - Cullen, G I
  - Cullen, James, Sr.
  - Culpepper Corporation
  - Cumberland Steel Co.
  - Cummin, John W
  - Cumming, Hugh S
  - Cummingham, Macklin
  - Cummings, Martin M
  - Cumpston, J H L
  - Cunningham, Gerald A
  - Curie Institute
  - Curlette & Co.
  - Curran J A
  - Current Biography
  - Currier, Raymond P
  - Curry, Manfred
  - Curry, Maria
  - Curtis Propeller Division
  - Curtis Publishing Company.
  - Curtis, Brown, LTD
  - Curtis, C D
  - Curtis, Charles
  - Cutting, Elizabeth
  - Cyclopedia of Medicine
  - Czekowitz, Marjorie F
  - DaCosta, J C JR.
  - Daily News
  - Daily Worker
  - Daily, Thomas M
  - Daland, Joseph
  - Daley, Adalene F
  - Dalhousie Review
  - Dalhousie University
  - Dallas Health Museum
  - Dallas, Wenzel
  - Daly, Charles C
  - Damarodas, Florence
  - Damrau, Frederic
  - Danaher, John A
  - Danaraji, T J
  - Danford, Eileen
  - Daniel, Joel R
  - Dann, Ruth E
  - Danner, Mrs. Jessie L
  - Danner, William M
  - Dannreuther, Walter T
  - D'Antoni, Joseph S
  - Darby Drug Company
  - Darby, Zadalia M
  - Darmstaetter, Armin A Jr.
  - Darnell-Smith, G P
  - Darrer, Enid E
  - Dartmouth Eye Institute
  - Das, A N
  - Davidson, M.T. Company
  - Davidson, Maurice P
  - Davidson, W T
  - Davies, Theo. H., & Co.
  - Davis, A Edward
  - Davis, Ada H
  - Davis, Allan
  - Davis, Charles F
  - Davis, E B
  - Davis, Edgar B
  - Davis, Ernest L
  - Davis, F A Company
  - Davis, George F
  - Davis, Herbert L
  - Davis, J G
  - Davis, Michael
  - Davis, Nora Lippi
  - Davis, R H
  - Davis, W Dewey
  - Davis, Warren B
  - Davis,Elmer
  - Davison, L L
  - Daviss, Helene
  - Dawson, A Ray
  - Dawson, Albert K
  - Day, Blanche
  - Day, John, Company, Inc., Publishers
  - Day, Leonard
  - Day, Nora Z
  - Day,Mrs. George parmly
  - De Graff, A H
  - Dean, Helen M
  - Dean, Margaret B
  - Dean, Mills
  - Dearborn National Casualty Co.
  - Deardorf
  - Debaun, Vincent C
  - Deering, Mrs. Frank
  - DeHeredia, Georgia
  - Dekaiser, Isaac
  - Dekay, Drake
  - DeKruif, Paul Henry
  - DeKuyper, John and Son
  - Del Castillo, Dr. and Mrs. Antonio
  - Delamater, Hazbrouck
  - Delano, Samuel
  - DeLaval sales & Service Inc.
  - Delp, Mrs. W D
  - Dembo, Fanny
  - Demopoulos, Victor
  - Denham, W Knox
  - Denison, Mr.
  - Denison, Winfred T
  - Deniston, George C
  - Denman, karl
  - Denney, Oscar E
  - Dennis, Irma S
  - Dennis, Joseph K., Co., Inc.
  - Dennison Manufacturing Co.
  - Denny, George V. Jr.
  - Denny, Mrs. George
  - Dent, M
  - Derryberry, Mayhew
  - Dershimer, F W
  - Detecto Scales, Inc.
  - Detroit (Michigan). Department of HEALTH
  - Deutsche Verlags-Anstalt GMBH
  - Deutschman, S
  - DeVilliers, Claire
  - Dewan Conference
  - Dick & Merle-Smith
  - Dick, Owen Bruce
  - Dick, Robert
  - Dicker, Helen
  - Dickinson, Walter B
  - Dictionary of American History
  - Didier, Publishers
  - Diebold Safe and Lock Co.
  - Dieck, Robert G
  - Diefendorf, Robert R
  - Dieschbourg, H
  - Digest, The
  - Dill, D B
  - Dimnet
  - Distler, John Cyrus
  - Dixie, Bureau
  - Doan, Charles A.
  - Doane, Gilbert H
  - Doane, Joseph C
  - Dobbins Mrg. Co.
  - Dobbins, W D
  - Docekal, Elizabeth C.
  - Dodd, Mead & Co.
  - Dodge, Bayard
  - Dodge, George C
  - Doefler, Leo G
  - Doherty, Edward John
  - Dominick, Sister M
  - Donahue, Elinor: Biographical Article on Dr. Heiser
  - Donahue, Loretta M.
  - Donaldson, Bessie M
  - Donaldson, Elizabeth
  - Donalisio, José
  - Donchian, Richard D
  - Doremus & Company
  - Dorey, Halstead
  - Dornufs, W J
  - Dorr Company
  - Dorsay, Richard
  - Doti, Mary L
  - Dotterer, Paul R
  - Doubleday, Doran and Company
  - Dougherty, Helen V
  - Douglas Gibbons & Co.
  - Douglas, Kittie G
  - Douglas, Mrs. Walter C
  - Douglass, Benjamin Wallace
  - Douglass, Edna
  - Doull, James A
  - Douris, Margaret
  - Dowd, Benjamin S Jr.
  - Dowling, Dr.
  - Dowling, J D
  - Downie, J W
  - Downing, Augustus S
  - Downs, E B
  - Dowson, Lytton H
  - Doxsee, Herald M
  - Doyle, Joseph
  - Doyle, Julia H
  - Drake, Mrs. William T
  - Drake, Ormand
  - Draper, Warren F
  - Drapkin, Julius
  - Drazin, Morris L
  - Dreher, O
  - Dreier, J C L
    See also: Business Transactions: Schall William & Co. - 34 Pierce, E. A., & Co. - 37, in:
  - Dreier, K S
  - Dreschler
  - Drexel, M
  - Drexel, Nellie D
  - Dreyfus, Mrs. George A
  - Drinker, Philip
  - Droke, Maxwell
  - Dryfus, M L
  - Dublin, Louis I
  - Dublin, Thomas D
  - DuBois, Wilbur L
  - Dubroff, I
  - Dubron, Bess
  - Dudderidge, Mary
  - Duffield, Thomas J
  - Dugan, Helen Mae
  - Dumm, C M
  - Dun and Bradstreet, Inc.
  - Dunbar Glass Corp.
  - Dungay, Neil S
  - Dunham, George C
  - Dunn, Evelyn
  - Dunn, James
  - Durand, Ruth
  - Duras, Colette de
  - Durfee, E C
  - Durrell, A E H
  - Duryea, Lyman C
  - Dutch, Leon Perry
  - Duvaller, Francois
  - Dwight, Marion E
  - Dwyer, Margaret M
  - Dwyer, Nelle C
  - Dyer, Brian
  - Dyke, Hamilton
  - E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company
  - Eadie, G A
  - East Tennessee Education Association
  - Eastman Kodak Company
  - Eastman Kodak Stores, Inc.
  - Eastman, Arthur B
  - Eastwood, Floyd R
  - Eaton, Helen S
  - Ebasco Services, Inc.
  - Eckerman, Gladys (re. estate of)
  - Eckes, Carol
  - Eckstein, Beatrice
  - Edgerly, Patricia
  - Edwards, Margaret
  - Eelman, P J
  - Egnes, D W
  - Eiman, John
  - Einert, Amy Christine
  - Einstein, A[lbert]
  - Einstein, Lewis
  - Eisenberg, Elaine
  - Eivenack, Hedy
  - Ekro Products Co.
  - Electric Specialty Company.
  - Electrical Refractories Co.
  - Electrolux Corporation
  - Elias, H L
  - Elkington, J S C
  - Ellert, John A
  - Ellicott, Anne Murray
  - Elliot, Mrs. Dennis
  - Elliott Service Co.
  - Ellis, Edward F
  - Ellis, Harry
  - Elson, Ida W
  - Elwell-Parker Electric Co.
  - Elwood, J W
  - Embree, Amy L
  - Embree, C A
  - Emerson, Galo P
  - Emerson, Haven
  - Emory, German H H
  - Empire City Publishing Co.
  - Employers' Mutual Fire Insurance
  - Employers' Mutual Liability Insurance Co. of Wisconsin
  - Employers Mutual of Wausau
  - Enfield, Charles D
  - Engineering Society of Detroit, Inc.
  - Englander, Charles
  - Ennis, Howard
  - Enniskillen, Mary
  - Enochs, MRS.
  - Entz, John F
  - Epstein, Max
  - Epworth Highroad
  - Ericksen, A N
  - Erickson, Evelyn
  - Erie County Anti-Vivisection Society
  - Erlich, Philip
  - Ermando, Papirio
  - Ermel, Elisabeth
  - Ermold, Edward, Co.
  - Ernest Distributing Co.
  - Ernst, Edward C
  - Erpf, Armand G
  - Estes, Grace W
  - Eugene Field Society
  - Euthanasia Society of America, Inc.
  - Evans, Allen
  - Evans, Frank
  - Evans, Guy C
  - Evans, Helen
  - Evans, J H
  - Evans, M J
  - Evans, Wainwright
  - Evaporated Milk Association
  - Ever Ready Label Corp.
  - Excel Shipping Company
  - Executive Health Report
  - E-Z mills, Inc.
  - Ezell, Stiles D
  - Fair, Kathryn
  - Fairbanks Co.
  - Fajardo, Jacabo
  - Falconer, Bolivar L
  - Falconer, Mrs.
  - Far Eastern Association of Tropical Medicine
  - Farber, Mrs. Joseph
  - Farbstein, Leonard
  - Farley, Louise
  - Farley, Philip H
  - Farley, Sister Mary Patrice
  - Farquharson, Marguerita McLean
  - Farrand Optical Co.
  - Farrar and Rinehart, Incorporated
  - Farrel-Birmingham Co.
  - Fasal, Paul
  - Faust, Juana
  - Feaskins, William B
  - Feck, L A
  - Fedders Corporation
  - Federal Security Agency
  - Federal Works Agency
  - Feintuch, Morris
  - Feld, Leonhard Felix
  - Feldman, Max
  - Feldman, Roger A
  - Felton, Jean Spencer
  - Felton, Lloyd D
  - Fenwick, Warren A
  - Ferguson, Dan
  - Ferguson, Mrs. J A
  - Fergusson, Daphne
  - Ferrari, Andres, Jr.
  - Ferrell, Dr.
  - Ferrell, Mrs. John A
  - Ferry, Quirino B
  - Few, Thomas
  - Fidelity-Philalphia Trust Company
  - Fieffer, Veronica M
  - Field, Henry
  - Fifth Avenue Hospital
  - Fight for Freedom, Inc.
  - Fine, Abraham
  - Finerty Chevrolet Corporation
  - Finlay, T Y
  - Finnish Employment Agency
  - Finucane, Bernard E
  - Firestone Tire and Rubber Co.
  - First National Bank of New Milford
  - Fischer, Adolphe E.
  - Fischer, Andrew L
  - Fischer, Arthur
  - Fischer, Helen C
  - Fishbein, Morris
  - Fisher, Carl G., Corporation
  - Fisher, Charles, Spring Corporation
  - Fisher, Clarence L
  - Fisher, Harry B
  - Fisher, Irving
  - Fisher's Island Country Club
  - Fiske, Annette
  - Fitch, F
  - Fitch, Francis T
  - Fitch, Ralph R
  - Fitzgerald, Alice
  - Fitzgerald, Florence
  - Fitzgerald, Margaret
  - Fitzpatrick, Mrs.
  - Flagler, Rachael F
  - Flaherty, Helen
  - Fleek
  - Fleming
  - Flemons, S
  - Flents Products, Co., Inc.
  - Fletcher, Henry Prather
  - Fletcher, Marion
  - Fletcher, Mrs. James
  - Fletcher, Sir Murchinson
  - Flexner, Abraham
  - Flexner, Simon
  - Flick, E C
  - Flint Journal
  - Flotats, Jaime
  - Fluck, Myrtle
  - Flynn, James M
  - Flynt, Mrs. Henry N
  - Focke, Theodore B
  - Fogel, Jeanne
  - Foker, Leslie W
  - Földes, J
  - Foley, John Patrick
  - Fonde, G H
  - Food Machinery Corp.
  - Foord, Edward
  - Foot Health Foundation
  - Forbes, Edward W
  - Forbes, Ellen
  - Forbes, JM & Co.
  - Forbes, Mrs. Henry S
  - Forbes, Mrs. Waldo
  - Forbes, Rose Dabney
  - Forbes, W Cameron
  - Ford, Charles A
  - Ford, Frank W
  - Ford, Stanley
  - Foree, James R
  - Foreign Policy Association.
  - Forman, Mary & Gerry
  - Forrest, Peter, Jr.
  - Forstat, Milton
  - Forster, Ernst
  - Forster, Florence E
  - Fort, Arthur G
  - Fortson, Lovick G
  - Fortune
  - Forum
  - Forum Lecture Bureau, Inc.
  - Foster Pump Works, Inc.
  - Foster, C B
  - Foster, Henry
  - Foster, Margery S
  - Foster, Mary Jane
  - Foster, Mary R
  - Four Wheel Drive Auto Co.
  - Fowler, George S
  - Fox, Austen H
  - Fox, Linda Beth
  - France, Beulah
  - Francis, Jean E
  - Frank, George I
  - Frankel, Walter K
  - Franklin Paint Co.
  - Franklin, Danny
  - Frantz, S.C., Co., Inc.
  - Fraser, W J
  - Frazier, Edith H
  - Frechou, Clemence
  - Freeman, Alice W
  - Freeman, Pearl
  - Freer, Marjorie Mueller
  - Frenzell, Mrs. John
  - Freth, Monica M
  - Freund, Alexander
  - Frey, G R
  - Frick, John H
  - Fricks, Grace B
  - Fricks, Mrs. L D
  - Fried, Lillian
  - Friedenthal, Wilhelm
  - Friedrich, Katherine
  - Frink, George k
  - Frissell, Sarah E
  - Fritz, Charles
  - Fritz, Howard W
  - Frost, Mary H
  - Frostilla Company, Inc.
  - Fuchs, Aldabert
  - Fuchs, Margaret (Mrs. Aldabert)
  - Fueller & Smith & Ross Inc.
  - Fuents Cha., Alfonso de la
  - Fujii, Minoru
  - Fuller Brush Company
  - Fuller Merriam Company
  - Fullerton, Mary M C
  - Funk, Forrest J
  - Furness Lines
  - Fussell, C F
  - Gabrille, Jon
  - Gachet, Rochelle Rod
  - Gafafer,W M
  - Gailey, Watson W
  - Gaines, Richard K
  - Gaines, Thomas
  - Gair, Robert, Co.
  - Galbraith, Mrs. B C
  - Gallager, Louise
  - Gallagher, James
  - Gallagher, W C
  - Gallardo, M M
  - Gannett, Lewis
  - Gans, Mrs. Hiram S
  - Garden State Parkway
  - Garfield Memorial Hospital
  - Garfunkel, Lillian
  - Garguilo, Henry
  - Garin, Dora
  - Garinger, G R
  - Gates, Arnold
  - Gates, Thomas S
  - Gati, Bela
  - Gauducheau, A
  - Gavin, Mrs. A
  - Gavron, Joseph
  - Geary, Sir William Nevill M
  - Gebhard, Bruno
  - Geer, Robert R
  - Gehant, Francis C
  - Gehramm, George H
  - Gehring, P
  - Gehrke, W R
  - Gehrmann, George H
  - Geier, Otto P
  - Geiges, Ellwood A
  - Gelb, Mrs. Louis
  - Geller, M
  - General Abrasive Company, Inc.
  - General American Process Equipment
  - General American Transportation Corp.
  - General Bronze Corporation
  - General Cable Corp.
  - General Electric Co.
  - General Fire Extinguisher Co.
  - General Food Sales Co., Inc.
  - General Foods Corporation.
  - General Machine Co.
  - General Machinery Corp.
  - General Mills, Inc.
  - General Motors Club,Baltimore
  - General Motors Corporation
  - Geneva (NY) Academy of Medicine
  - Gensler, Evelyn
  - George A. Bates Society, Tufts College
  - George, Jesse
  - Georgia Warm Springs Foundation
  - Gerard Publishing Co.
  - Gerdes & Co., Inc
  - Gerdney
  - Gerénte, Henri
  - Geriatric Pharmaceuticals, Inc.
  - Gerken, Edna A
  - German Hospital - Horace E. Smith
  - German, H W
  - Gerow, Alice H
  - Gershon-Cohen, J
  - Gerster, John C A
  - Gett, Harold P
  - Giacomini, Lynwood
  - Giarraputo, Jerry
  - Gibbs, Mrs. William Francis
  - Gilbert, Clayton D
  - Gilbert, Mrs. Olive E
  - Gilchrist, W A
  - Giles, Ray
  - Gillespie, Alan K
  - Gillespie, T M
  - Gillette Safety Razor Co.
  - Gillette,H M
  - Gilman, M
  - Gilmore, John
  - Ginor, Richard
  - Ginsberg, Sarah
  - Ginsburg & Levy, Inc.
  - Ginsburg, Margot
  - Giobel, Marjorie
  - Girard College
  - Gjesdahl, Mrs. Grace Konold
  - Gladstone, Henry
  - Glass, Anna M
  - Glass, James H
  - Glennon, A H
  - Glenny, Charlotte
  - Glenwood Range Co.
  - Glick, Harry S
  - Globe American Corp.
  - Globe and Mail
  - Globe Magazines, Inc.
  - Goelet, Mrs.
  - Goffen, Bernard S
  - Golden Crown Mining Co.
  - Goldfader, Philip
  - Goldman, Alexander
  - Goldschmidt, Erna
  - Goldstein, Eleanor B
  - Goldstein, Sarah Miller
  - Goldwag, Harry L
  - Goldwater, Leonard J
  - Goldwater, S G
  - Gomez, Evangelina V de
  - Gonzales,Emma
  - Good Teeth Council
  - Goodell, Charles E
  - Goodenow, Frank J
  - Goodhart, Robert S
    See also: Vivisection, in:
  - Goodhart, Robert S
  - Goodlight, Theresa B
  - Goodman, Nathan G
  - Goodman, Sara
  - Goodner, Kenneth
  - Goodney, Benjamin
  - Goodrich, David M
  - Goodridge, Malcolm
  - Goodstein, Iris
  - Goodwill Industries
  - Goodwin, Frank
  - Gordon, H L
  - Gordon, Hugh H Jr.
  - Gordon, R M
  - Gordon, Robert K
  - Gorgas, General Personal Traits as described by Dr. Heiser
  - Gosse, Philip
  - Gossman, H Peter
  - Gostalowsky, Maurice D
  - Gottesman, Annabelle
  - Gottschalk, Helen R
  - Gould All-Day, Inc.
  - Gould, Wilbur James
  - Gowen, Harriet E
  - Goy W., & Co.
  - Grable, Bennis E
  - Grace, Arthur W
  - Grace, P H
  - Graff, E G
  - Graham, Gladys Fisher
  - Graham, J D
  - Graham, Lady
  - Graham, Mrs. Alfred H
  - Graham, Sir James
  - Grand Valley Oil Corp.
  - Grand View Cemetery - Johnstown
  - Grant, Cora
  - Grant, Elinor
  - Grant, H G
  - Grant, John B
  - Grant, Joseph
  - Grant, Mrs. Herbert
  - Graves Taylor & Associates
  - Gray, C J
  - Gray, David
  - Gray, Mrs. E B
  - Great Northern Railway Company
  - Greater New York Dietetic Association
  - Green County (NY) Tuberculosis and public Health Association
  - Green, Barbara
  - Green, Etta Coulter
  - Green, L E
  - Green, Leona Thacher
  - Green, Margaret Frances
  - Green, Mrs. Howard Whipple
  - Green, Myron B
  - Green, Theodore Francis
  - Greenbelt Health Association
  - Greenberg, Abe S
  - Greenberg, Leonard
  - Greene, R L
  - Greene, Roger S
  - Greenman, Bess
  - Greer, D Newton
  - Gregson, John F
  - G-R-I Pharmaceuticals Inc.
  - Gridley, Mrs. L B
  - Gries, Jeanie
  - Griffenhagen & Associates
  - Griffith, Henry M
  - Griffith, J Neal
  - Griffith, John
  - Griffith, Mrs. A M
  - Griffith, Mrs. Doyle
  - Griggs, Stella
  - Grill, Julia Kiriloff
  - Grimes, Charles W
  - Griswold, Don M
  - Groak, Rose
  - Groebel, Sally Wesserzieher
  - Groost, Mrs. S
  - Gross, Henry M
  - Gross, Ludwik
  - Grossett & Dunlap, Inc.
  - Grotner, Ross A Jr.
  - Grotzert, Jack M
  - Group Health Cooperative, Inc.
  - Groves, I K
  - Grubbs, Daniel
  - Grubbs, Mrs. Frank R
  - Grubbs, S B
  - Gruber, Rudolf E
  - Guaranty Loan & Trust Co.
  - Guaranty Trust Co.
  - Guccione, D J
  - Guerra, Francisco
  - Guggenheim (John Simon) Memorial Foundation.
  - Gulf States Paper Corp.
  - Gulick, Sidney L
  - Gumprich, Mrs. O
  - Gunlocke, W. H., Chair Company
  - Gunn, J A
  - Gunn, Kenneth W
  - Gunn, S V
  - Gunn, Selskar
  - Gunter Hotel
  - Gunther, John
  - Gutmann, Ferdimand, & Co.
  - Gutterson, Walter C
  - Haas, Marjorie, and Harry
  - Habas, Ralph A.
  - Haber, Kraditor
  - Hackett, John T
  - Hackett, Lewis W
  - Hadassah
  - Haddock, H J
  - Hadfield, Lady
  - Hadley, Hamilton
  - Haffenden, C R
  - Haftel, Bruno B
  - Hagadeon, Bertha W
  - Hagaman, Ida M
  - Hagan, Loree
  - Hagen, Robert S
  - Hagins, John W
  - Haglage, Dorothy
  - Haguewood, E E
  - Hahn, Rosina
  - Haight, A. A., * Co.
  - Haimes, Leonard P
  - Haiti, President's Commission for the Study and Review of Conditions
  - Halberstadt, Ernst
  - Hale, Richard W
  - Hall of Fame
  - Hall Planetary Co.
  - Hall, Albert W
  - Hall, Bolton
  - Hall, Cappel
  - Hall, Charles R
  - Hall, Frank B., & Co.
  - Hall, Fred S
  - Hall, Henry N Jr.
  - Hall, Thomas
  - Hall, Vesta K
  - Hall, William Edwin
  - Halley, Ernest P
  - Halliday, Thomas G
  - Halsey, Robert Hurtin
  - Hamakami, Lynette
  - Hambidge, Gove, Article on Dr. Heiser
  - Hamblin, Cornelia B
  - Hamilton Watch Company
  - Hamilton, Mrs. Alexander
  - Hamlin, C S
  - Hammarlund Mfg. Co.
  - Hamor, Pauline
  - Hampden County (Mass.) Tuberculosis Association
  - Hancock, Linda M
  - Handel, Selma
  - Handy, Dora Keen
  - Haney, John L
  - Haney, Ruth Louise
  - Hankemeyer, Natalie
  - Hann & Hann
  - Hanna, A J
  - Hanna, Mabel
  - Harbater, Melvin
  - Harbaugh, C R
  - Harbord, James G
  - Harcourt, Brace, Jovanovich, Inc.
  - Hardee, Walter P
  - Harder, Mrs. Victor
  - Hardin, E D
  - Harding,Delma E
  - Hariton, Sol
  - Harkness, Robert
  - Harley, Hugh
  - Harmony, Francessa Cunningham
  - Harnsberger, James P
  - Harper and Brothers
  - Harper, Agnes M
  - Harper, R M
  - Harrar, J G
  - Harriman, Averell
  - Harris, Anna F
  - Harris, Kerr, Forster & Co.
  - Harris, Robert S
    See: Journal of Experimental Med., in:
  - Harris, Roger
  - Harris, Seale
  - Harrison, Francis Burton
  - Harrison, Paul
  - Hart, Charles D
  - Hart, S Alton
  - Hartford Accident and Indemnity
  - Hartman, Ralph D
  - Harvard Club of NYC
  - Harvard University
  - Harvey, Bartle T
  - Harvey, D
  - Haskin Information Service
  - Hassall, John, Inc.
  - Hasselmann, C M
  - Hasseltine, H E
  - Hatch, Theodore
  - Hatcher, James B
  - Hathaway, Conrad P
  - Hathaway, Mrs. Conrad P
  - Hatrick, Harold F
  - Hattery, Stella B
  - Hauck Mfg Co.
  - Haug, George & Co Inc.
  - Haughwout, Frank
  - Hausman, Harry
  - Haussermann, John W
  - Havre, J B
  - Hawkes, E Zeh
  - Hawkins, Glenn J
  - Hawkridge, Mrs. Leslie D
  - Hawley, Lauinia
  - Hay, Cutler
  - Hay, R C B
  - Hayes, Chester
  - Hayes, Wilhelmina C
  - Hayhurst, Emery R
  - Hayles, C V
  - Hayman, Ben
  - Hayward, Leland, Inc.
  - Hayward, Mary (Mrs Walter)
  - Hazard Editorial Offices
  - Headlee, Thomas J
  - Healey, Sam
  - Health League of Canada
  - Health of Our Industrial Soldiers.
  - Health Service in Industry
  - Hearing Aids
  - Hearne, William L
  - Heart Disease Control Program
  - Heath, Ellen
  - Heath, Mrs. Herbert L
  - Hecht, Otto
  - Heckel, Mrs. M
  - Hedge, L R
  - Hedges, Ida Jane
  - Hedstrom, Sir Maynard
  - Heil, Sylvia
  - Heiligman, N H
  - Heimishemeyer, L Arthur
  - Heinemann, William, Ltd.
  - Heinsohn, E C
  - Heiser Foundation, Inc.
  - Heiser, Arthur
  - Heiser, Carl
  - Heiser, Elizabeth
  - Heiser, Jenny
  - Heiser, Joseph
  - Heiser, Karl F
  - Heiser, Louis
  - Heiser, Marion (as Marion Peterson Phinny)
  - Heiser, Toni
  - Heiser, Victor G.
  - Hellendall, R
  - Heller, Mary
  - Helm, Blanche
  - Helmers Mfg. Co
  - Helmers, Mrs. W C
  - Helms, Marjorie
  - Helvie, Clara Cook
  - Hempstead and Son
  - Hendes, Edelmira D
  - Henry Holt and Company
  - Henry, J Norman
  - Henry, Miss
  - Henschkel, Harvey C
  - Hentz, H. & Co.
  - Hepford, David
  - Herald Printing Co.
  - Herald Tribune
  - Herbut, Peter A
  - Hercules Expansion Plug Mfg. Co. Inc
  - Hercus, C E
  - Herdman, Doris M
  - Herdman, Ramona
  - Herendeen, F W
  - Heritage Foundation
  - Herman, Alex
  - Herman, Coralie
  - Hernando, Eugenio
  - Herrick, Frederick C
  - Herriot, Roger M
  - Hertslet, L E
  - Hertz, Walter
  - Herzog, George
  - Hess, Mrs. Alfred F (Sara Straus)
  - Hesseltine, H E
  - Hessler, Robert
  - Heuman, Oral K
  - Hewer, A M
  - Hewitt, Edward R
  - Hewitt, Rubber Corporation
  - Heyman, Gertrude
  - Heyser, Carl J Jr.
  - Hidden, Kate H A
  - Higgins, Margaret
  - Higgins, Norman N
  - Hill, Anna
  - Hill, Harwood
  - Hill, M Wood
  - Hillgrove, Katherine E
  - Hills Bros. Coffee, Inc.
  - Hillsman, J R
  - Himler, L E
  - Hineline, Flora
  - Hinkel, William
  - Hirschmann, Kurt
  - Hiscock, Ira V
  - Hiser, W S
  - Hitchcock, Curtice
  - Hitchcock, Luella L
  - Hobart Manufacturing Co.
  - Hoben, E W
  - Hochlerner, R
  - Hodgolon, Hazel L
  - Hodgson, Caspar W
  - Hodgson, Edna
  - Hoehn, Matther
  - Hoffman, G
  - Hoffman, H F
  - Hoffman-LaRoche Inc.
  - Höjer, Axel
  - Hoke, Ann
  - Holl, Jack M
  - Holland Society of New York
  - Hollenbeck, Alta
  - Holligan, L E
  - Hollingsworth, Betty
  - Hollingsworth,Ann
  - Hollis, William H
  - Holloway, Jack
  - Holm, Elizabeth M
  - Holmes, Burton
  - Holmes, Elizabeth O'Keefe
  - Holmes, John Haynes
  - Holmsen, Ellen
  - Holston Ordinance Works
  - Holt, Mrs. Herbert H
  - Holt, Mrs. Rackham
  - Holt, Mrs. Robert H
  - Holt, Rackham
  - Homblad, Edward C
  - Honey, Robert E
  - Hooper, Frances
  - Hooper, Mabel
  - Hoops, A L
  - Hoover Ball and Bearing Co.
  - Hopkins, Constance C
  - Hopkins, Mrs. Ralph
  - Hopkins, Ralph
  - Hopper, E W
  - Horn, A C
  - Hornick, Leander G
  - Hornstein, S L
  - Horovitz, Mrs. Henry I
  - Horovitz, Natalie Dorin
  - Horton, Holbrook L
  - Horwath, Ernest B
  - Horwitz, Alfred S
  - Hosch, Louis
  - Hosdreg Company, Inc.
  - Hospital Association of New York State
  - Hospital Council of Greater New York
  - Hotchkiss, H Stuart
  - Hottenstein, Esther
  - Hough, Mary
  - Houghton Mifflin Company
  - Houston Ready Cut House Co.
  - Houston Shipbuilding Corp.
  - Hoving, Thomas P F
  - Howard, William Vaughn
  - Howell, W H
  - Howland, Alice
  - Howland, Llewellyn
  - HSMHA Health Service
  - Hubbell, May Gifford
  - Hubert, T H
  - Hudson, Ellis Herndon
  - Hudson, Mary Catherine
  - Huffman, George A
  - Hughes, Phyllis
  - Hughes, R M
  - Hughes, Thomas J
  - Huhner, Max
  - Huie, J Howard
  - Huizenga, Lee S
  - Human Betterment Association
  - Human Engineering Foundation
  - Hunt, Alice
  - Hunt, Mrs. Edward Eyre
  - Hunt, Virginia L
  - Hunter Razor Co.
  - Hunter, Joseph R
  - Hunter, Susan Frances
  - Hunting, Harold B
  - Huntington, F W
  - Huska, John
  - Hussey, Marguerite M
  - Hussey, Raymond
  - Hutchings, Richard H
  - Hutchins, Mrs.
  - Hutton, E. F. & Company, Inc.
  - Hutton, William
  - Hyde, Eric F
  - Hydrick, J L
  - Hydrick, John
  - Hygrade Sylvania Corporation
  - Hyman, Harold Thomas
  - Hyman, John E
  - IAS Personnel Bureau
  - Idaho.Department of Public Health
  - Illinois Manufacturers Association
  - Illinois State Nurses' Association
  - Illinois Stock Transfer Company
  - Illinois. Department of Public Health
  - Illnesses
  - Illustre, Ernesto D